(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-02T21:25:45.728528",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Ah, whipしたケーキのような街は
Ah, the whipped cake-like town is
好き! 雪! 本気マジック
So much! Snow! True magic!
空がくれるコンフェッティは冬のフェスタ 祝う天使の羽よ woo
Confetti from the sky is a winter festa, blessing angel wings, woo!
白銀の国へ出かけるの go, go, go
Heading out to the silver-white land, go, go, go!
雪の汽車が街を駆け choo, choo, choo
The snow train dashes through town, choo, choo, choo!
絵本みたいな景色を君に見せてあげるから
I'll show you a scenery straight out of a picture book.
願い込めこめて 呪文さあ(さあ) 歌って(さん はい)
Pour in your wish, cast a spell—come on (come on), sing along (three, two, one)!
a, b, c, d ドド シシ ララ シシ マジカル ミラクルクル pop
A, B, C, D, do-do, si-si, la-la, si-si, magical miracle pop!
Ah, whipしたケーキのような街は
Ah, the whipped cake-like town is
好き! 雪! 本気マジック
So much! Snow! True magic!
空がくれるコンフェッティは冬のフェスタ 祝う天使の羽よ
Confetti from the sky is a winter festa, blessing angel wings.
light upしたオーロラ色の街は
The light-up aurora-colored town is
好き! 雪! 本気マジック
So much! Snow! True magic!
子供でいられたら dream land
If we could stay kids, it's a dream land.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to Snow Miku!
ツンと冷たい季節が好き love, love, love
I love the sharp, cold season, love, love, love!
アイスも魔法もとけないように ヒュー ヒュー ヒュー
So that neither ice nor magic melts, hyuu, hyuu, hyuu!
ずっとこのままじゃダメなのはやっぱりドキドキしたいな
Staying like this forever just won't do—I want to feel my heart race!
未来求め呪文今(な う) 歌って(さん はい)
Seeking the future, cast a spell now (now), sing along (three, two, one)!
1, 2, 3, 4 水金地火木 マジカル ミラクルクル pop
1, 2, 3, 4, Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Jupiter, magical miracle pop!
Ah ホップしたウサギのような気分
Ah, feeling like a hopping rabbit,
好き! 雪! 本気マジック
So much! Snow! True magic!
大地がくれる元気得たら 思い通り明日を生きていけるよ
Once you get energy from the earth, you can live tomorrow just as you wish.
まぶしい白に染まるハート 君に
A heart dyed in dazzling white, for you—
好き! 雪! 本気マジック
So much! Snow! True magic!
大人のふりなんていいじゃん
Pretending to be an adult is totally fine!
I hear that beat from town, The cute angel will come down
This is my home I'll let you know, Namara fantastic!
The snowscape is lyrical, The street gonna be magical
I'll set you free in my land, oh, oh, oh, oh
今日の寒さも忘れるように(忘れるように)
So we can forget today's cold (so we can forget it),
悩みだって悩みだって 凍らせて消せる魔力よ(もっかい)
The magical power to freeze and erase all worries (once more)!
a, b, c, d ドド シシ ララ シシ マジカル ミラクルクル pop
A, B, C, D, do-do, si-si, la-la, si-si, magical miracle pop!
Ah, whipしたケーキのような街は
Ah, the whipped cake-like town is
好き! 雪! 本気マジック
So much! Snow! True magic!
空がくれるコンフェッティは冬のフェスタ 祝う天使の羽よ
Confetti from the sky is a winter festa, blessing angel wings.
light upしたオーロラ色の街は
The light-up aurora-colored town is
好き! 雪! 本気マジック
So much! Snow! True magic!
子供でいられたら dream land
If we could stay kids, it's a dream land.
いいじゃん!
That's fine!
1, 2, 3, 4 水金地火木 マジカル ミラクルクル pop
1, 2, 3, 4, Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Jupiter, magical miracle pop!
Ah ホップしたウサギのような気分
Ah, feeling like a hopping rabbit,
好き! 雪! 本気マジック
So much! Snow! True magic!
大地がくれる元気得たら 思い通り明日を生きていけるよ
Once you get energy from the earth, you can live tomorrow just as you wish.
まぶしい白に染まるハート 君に
A heart dyed in dazzling white, for you—
好き! 雪! 本気マジック
So much! Snow! True magic!
大人のふりなんていいじゃん
Pretending to be an adult is totally fine!
I hear that beat from town, The cute angel will come down
This is my home I'll let you know, Namara fantastic!
The snowscape is lyrical, The street gonna be magical
I'll set you free in my land, oh, oh, oh, oh
今日の寒さも忘れるように(忘れるように)
So we can forget today's cold (so we can forget it),
悩みだって悩みだって 凍らせて消せる魔力よ(もっかい)
The magical power to freeze and erase all worries (once more)!
a, b, c, d ドド シシ ララ シシ マジカル ミラクルクル pop
A, B, C, D, do-do, si-si, la-la, si-si, magical miracle pop!
Ah, whipしたケーキのような街は
Ah, the whipped cake-like town is
好き! 雪! 本気マジック
So much! Snow! True magic!
空がくれるコンフェッティは冬のフェスタ 祝う天使の羽よ
Confetti from the sky is a winter festa, blessing angel wings.
light upしたオーロラ色の街は
The light-up aurora-colored town is
好き! 雪! 本気マジック
So much! Snow! True magic!
子供でいられたら dream land
If we could stay kids, it's a dream land.
いいじゃん!
That's fine!
さあ クリスマス いっぱいのかわいい
Come on, full of Christmas cuteness
君に届けんだ パーティー ナイト
Delivering it to you on this party night
さあ クリスマス いっぱいのお願い
Come on, full of Christmas wishes
君に誓うんだ ホーリー ホーリー ナイト
Swearing to you on this holy, holy night
今年のクリスマス ちょっと特別さ
This year's Christmas is a bit special
ホワイトクリスマスじゃないだって
Even if it's not a white Christmas
星屑のイルミネーション
Stardust illumination
ほら ふりつもるよ
Look, it's piling up
キラキラ 輝いて みんなが幸せで
Sparkling and shining, everyone being happy
メリー クリスマス!
Merry Christmas!
見ってる?
Are you watching?
チョコ先生のさっきのサンタ衣装と、
We swapped Choco-sensei's Santa outfit
メル様の雪だるま衣装、交換してみました！
with Mel-sama's snowman outfit!
イエーイ！可愛いでしょう？
Yay! Isn't it cute?
どうかな？どうかな？
What do you think?
めちゃめちゃ可愛くない？この衣装！
Isn't this outfit super cute?
いっぱい写真撮って、いっぱい曲の感想ツイートしてほしいな。
Take lots of photos and tweet your thoughts on the songs!
このハッシュタグでよろしくね！お願いします！
Please use this hashtag! Thank you!
この後もね、いっぱい楽しい曲が続くから、
There are lots of fun songs coming up after this,
みんなもいっぱい声出して、お家でね、サイリウムとか振って楽しんでってね！
so be sure to cheer along, wave your glow sticks at home, and have fun!
よろしくお願いします！よろしくお願いします！
Thank you so much! Thank you!
じゃあチョコ先生、そろそろ次の曲行きますか？行っちゃいますか？
Well then, Choco-sensei, shall we move on to the next song? Shall we go?
レッツ ゴー！
Let's go!
ハッとするような情景が
A scene that takes your breath away,
パッと消えそうな心象が
A fleeting mental image,
ぼくあたしのファインダーを満たしてキレイさ
Fulfills my viewfinder so prettily.
どうでもいいけど
Whatever, though!
パシャりキラリ
Snap and sparkle,
フワりもったり
Fluffy and sluggish,
背伸びナウ天使ワールド
Striving now in the angel world.
不安定ジブン愛して欲が
An unstable self loving and wanting
「見せたい!」クレッシェンド
A crescendo of "I want to show you!"
流行りつまり似たりよったり加工した少ないワールド
A trendy, copy-paste processed shallow world.
飾らないキミを愛した熱も「いらない!」デクレッシェンド
A decrescendo discarding the passion of loving unadorned you.
味わう前に口に出しちゃうラブはインスタント
Love that spills out before savored is instant.
キミのハートすら欲しくなっちゃう今日も
Even wanting your heart today as well.
映えテクスタディGO!
Insta-study, go!
こうやってかっこよく加工すればたくさんいいねをもらえるのか？
If I process it to look cool like this, will I get lots of likes?
よし、チョコもかこっ…どうだ？
Alright, Choco will process it too... How's this?
あれ？寄り過ぎた？
Huh? Is it too close?
いいね! いいね! 愛してみても いいね? いいね? どうぞお好きに
Likes! Likes! Even if you try trying, do as you please!
いいね! いいね! 実ははどうでも いいね! いいね! スキもキラいも
Likes! Likes! Actually, whatever! Likes! Likes! Both likes and dislikes.
ハッとするような情景が
A scene that takes your breath away,
パッと消えそうな心象が
A fleeting mental image,
濁った日々のファインダーを
Blur the viewfinder of murky days
ぼかしてキレイだな
And make it look pretty.
サッと繋がる感情も
Even emotions that connect in a flash,
キミに届けたアイラブユーも
And the "I love you" delivered to you,
本当はもっと違ってたんだって
Were actually supposed to be different.
どうでもいいけどどうでもいいけど
Whatever, though, whatever, though.
流行り？ファッション？イマイチわかんない
Trends? Fashion? I don't really get it,
でもちょっと手を伸ばしてオシャれ！あたしだってできるはずなんだまずは最初の第一歩
But reaching out a bit to be stylish! I should be able to do it too, first step!
手軽に思おう気軽に投稿こんなあたしもおイケなエフェクトかけて登頂したいのヘブン！
Thinking casually, posting easily, I want to reach the peak with cool effects too, heaven!
思い立ったらす即登録！
Registering immediately on an impulse!
タグ付けする友達がいない！！
I have no friends to tag!!
位置情報？あい地図読めない！！
Location info? I can't read maps!!
これがSNSワールドの洗礼か
Is this the baptism of the SNS world?
必死にサバイブ＆エフォートあたしはここだよ見てくれ世間ッ
Desperately surviving & effort, I'm right here, look at me, world!
気になったなら押して押されてsay！！いいね！スキの音で跳ねる衝動だけでいいや
If you're curious, press and be pressed and say!! Likes! Just the impulse of bouncing to the sound of love is fine.
なんて思うのにさ映る方向までついつい追っかっちゃうよ
But even while thinking that, I end up chasing right up to the camera angle.
いいねいいねもっともらえたら いいねいいね不純だっていいよ
Likes, likes, if I get more, likes, likes, even impurity is fine.
インスタントな魔法でぼくらちょっと繋がれるんだ
With instant magic, we can connect just a little bit.
おもち！
Omochi!
いいね! いいね! まったくれたら いいね! いいね! 不純だっていいよ インスタントな魔法で
Likes! Likes! If you give me more, likes! likes! Even if impure, with instant magic
ぼくらちょっと繋がれるんだ
We can connect a little bit.
いいね! いいね! 愛してみても いいね? いいね? どうぞお好きに いいね! いいね! マジでどうでも
Likes! Likes! Even if you try loving, likes? likes? Do as you please! Likes! Likes! Seriously whatever!
いいね! いいね! ラブの数とか
Likes! Likes! The number of loves, etc.
ハッとするような情景が
A scene that takes your breath away,
パッと消えそうな心象が
A fleeting mental image,
ぼくあたしのファインダーを満たしてキレイさ
Fulfills my viewfinder so prettily.
どうでもいいことも追いかけて共有して
Chasing and sharing even unimportant things,
笑った感情は本当なんだからもう映え映えとしたヘブンなんて
The smiling emotions are real, so no more flashy, picture-perfect "heaven" stuff
どうでもいいからどうでもいいけど
Is whatever, because whatever, though!
ハッとするような情景が
A scene that makes you gasp,
パッと消えそうなお心気が
a fleeting state of mind,
ぼくあたし側のファインダーを満たしてキレイさ
filling the viewfinder on my side, making it beautiful.
どう でも いい けど
Any which way is fine, but
いいね！いいね！
Nice! Nice!
ハッとするような情景が
A scene that makes you gasp,
パッと消えそうなお心気が
a fleeting state of mind,
キラリ光る 白い雪が
Sparkling and shining, the white snow
少しずつ街を染めていくさ
slowly dyes the town little by little.
二人で奏でるメロディ
The melody we play together,
探しに出かけよう
let's go out and search for it.
この冬 最後の雪が
The last snow of this winter
僕らの街に舞い降りた
has fluttered down onto our town.
二人が歩いた道の 足跡は消えてしまう
The footprints of the path we walked together disappear.
冷たい空気吸い込んで
Breathing in the cold air,
泣き出しそうな空を見た
I looked at the sky that looked ready to cry.
明日の朝には二人 別々の場所へ歩き出す
Tomorrow morning, the two of us will start walking to different places.
臆病すぎた僕は 大事なことも言えず
Being too cowardly, I couldn't even say what mattered most,
震える君のその手を 握る事さえも…
and couldn't even hold your trembling hand...
キラリ光る 白い雪が
Sparkling and shining, the white snow
少しずつ街を染めていくさ
slowly dyes the town little by little.
二人で奏でるメロディ
The melody we play together,
探しに出かけよう
let's go out and search for it.
長い夢が覚める前に この想い君に届けたい
Before this long dream awakens, I want to convey these feelings to you.
きっと、また新しい歌声が この空に舞い降りる
Surely, a brand new singing voice will flutter down from this sky.
この冬 最後の風が
The last wind of this winter
僕らの街を吹き抜けた
blew through our town.
枯れ木に宿る蕾が 春の訪れを告げる
The buds dwelling on the withered trees announce the arrival of spring.
おどけた顔で誤魔化して うつむく僕を窘めた
You chided me as I hung my head, playing it off with a playful face.
去年冬より少し 大人びた君のその笑顔
Your smiling face, slightly more mature than last winter.
不器用すぎた僕は 大事なこと見落とし
Being too clumsy, I overlooked the most important thing,
こぼれる君の涙に 気づくことさえも…
and couldn't even notice your spilling tears...
ヒラリ落ちる 白い雪が
Gently falling, the white snow
少しずつ頬を染めていく
slowly dyes our cheeks little by little.
もう、二人で奏でるリズム 途切れないように、
So that the rhythm we play together will never be cut short,
キラリ光る 白い雪が
Sparkling and shining, the white snow
少しずつ空へ溶けていく
slowly melts away into the sky.
ねえ、二人で奏でたメロディ 忘れはしないよ
Hey, I will never forget the melody we played together.
長い夢が覚める頃に 君はもう消えてしまうけど
When this long dream awakens, you will already have vanished, but
きっと、また懐かしい歌声が 新しい未来で
surely, that nostalgic singing voice once more in a new future
光り輝く雪になって この空に舞い降りる
will become glowing snow and flutter down from this sky.
やがて目の前に舞い降りる
And soon flutter down right before my eyes.
ヒラリ落ちる 白い雪が
Gently falling, the white snow
少しずつ頬を染めていく
slowly dyes our cheeks little by little.
もう、二人で奏でるリズム 途切れないように
So that the rhythm we play together will never be cut short,
ずっとキラリ光る 白い雪が
Always sparkling and shining, the white snow
少しずつ空へとけてゆくねえ
slowly melts away into the sky, hey,
二人で奏でたメロディ 忘れはしないよ
I will never forget the melody we played together.
長い夢が覚める頃に 君はもう消えてしまうけど
When this long dream awakens, you will already have vanished, but
きっと、また懐かしい歌声が 新しい未来で
surely, that nostalgic singing voice once more in a new future
光り輝く雪になって この空に舞い
will become glowing snow and dance in this sky...
キラリ光る 白い雪が
Sparkling and glittering, the gleaming white snow
少しずつ街を染めていく
gently, little by little, colours the town.
さあ、二人で奏でるメロディー 探しに出かけよう
come on, let's go and find the melody we'll play together.
じゃあね、こっからはなんと
So, from here on...
撮影コーナーに入りまーす！やったー！
We're entering the photoshoot corner! Yay!
イェーイ！イェーイ！
Yay! Yay!
ってことで、えーフォロワーのね
So, um, for our followers...
え、何人かにちょっと来てもらって、メルたちにとって欲しいポーズを指定してもらってですね
we invited a few of them to come and specify the poses they want us to strike,
可愛いポーズをいっぱい撮りたいと思いますので、ちょっとね、着替えてきたいと思います。
and we want to take lots of cute poses, so we're going to go change our outfits.
はい！ってことで待っててくださいね！待っててね！
Yes! So please wait for us! Wait for us!
着替えてきたよ！みんなお待たせ！
We've changed! Thanks for waiting, everyone!
お待たせ！
Thanks for waiting!
メルサンタと、じゃーん！
Mel-Santa and, ta-da!
チョコサンタです！イェーイ！
Choco-Santa! Yay! Yay!
じゃあね、早速1人目お呼びしたいと思います。
Now then, let's call our first person right away.
はい！1人目はこの方！この方！
Yes! The first person is... this person!
ケーキ！
Cake!
メリークリスマス！キアラちゃん！
Merry Christmas! Kiara-chan!
メリッ！うっかりクリスマス！
Merry! Oops, Merry Christmas!
サンタクロースのお二人ですか？可愛い！
Are you two Santa Claus? So cute!
そうだよ！だからチキンちょうだい！
That's right! So give us some chicken!
そうよ！よこしなさいよ！よこせ！よこせ！
That's right! Hand it over! Hand it over! Hand it over!
私、不死鳥なんでチキンはちょっとお渡しできないんですけどもー！
I'm a phoenix, so I can't really give you chicken...
えーと、海外のミームを真似してもらいたいなと思って来ましたけど
Um, I came hoping you'd imitate a foreign meme,
どうですかね？ビームそうそうそう、とある海外のアニメのポーズを真似してもらいたいです、2人で！できるかな？
how is that? Yes, yes, yes, I want you two to imitate a pose from a certain foreign anime! Can you do it?
オッケー！オッケーオッケーオッケー！
Okay! Okay, okay, okay!
そしたら、1人死にかけるようなキャラクターが必要なんですけど、死にかけた人誰ですか？
Then, we need a character who's about to die. Who's the person who dies?
じゃあチョコ死にかけます！
Then Choco will die!
死にかけチョコ先、床に倒れて欲しいです、まず。
Choco-sensei about to die, I want you to collapse on the floor first.
そうそうそうそう、上向きですね。体、体、そうそう、そうそうそう、いい感じ。オッケー。
That's right, facing upwards. Body, body, yes, yes, yes, feels good. Okay.
で、そしたらメル先輩には、チョコ先​​の隣に来て欲しいんですけど、そうそうそこそこ。可愛い可愛い。で、隣でしゃがんで欲しいです。
And then, Mel-senpai, I want you to come next to Choco-sensei, right there. Cute, cute. And I want you to crouch next to her.
はい！そう、そんな感じ。もうちょっと近くかな？
Yes! Right, like that. A bit closer maybe?
イエスエスエス、イエス！で、そこで、えーと、そうそう、考えろチョコ、考えろみたいなポーズをとって欲しい、そういうことです。
Yes, yes, yes, yes! And then, um, strike a pose like 'Think, Choco, think,' something like that.
もうバッチリです！セリフだけ言っててもらいたいな、あの英語で
That's spot on! I just want you to say your lines in English—
'Think, Choco, think'って言って欲しい、怒った顔で。怒って。
'Think, Choco, think,' with an angry face. Get angry.
'Think, Choco, think!'
やったー！すっごい！これをね、レリドーでいっぱいのせてもらえそう！レットピクチャプリン！
Yay! Amazing! You can put so much of this in Lallitour! Let's picture, please!
オッケー、オッケー！もう一個あるけど
Okay, okay! There's one more, but
もう1個の方はもうちょっと簡単だと思う。まず隣に立って欲しいです。
the other one is a bit easier, I think. First, I want you to stand next to each other.
はい。で、チョコ先​​、えっと、右腕を、メル先輩の背中にのせてほしい。そうそうそうそう、後ろ、後ろ、後ろで。
Yes. And Choco-sensei, um, please put your right arm on Mel-senpai's back. Yes, right there, in the back, in the back.
そう、で、左腕は、なんかメル先輩に何か遠いものを見せてるように、そうそうそうそうそう！
Right, and for your left arm, make it look like you're showing Mel-senpai something far away, yes, exactly!
で、チョコ先​​は嬉しい顔で、メル先輩は怖い顔で、やばいみたいな。マジかよみたいな。
And Choco-sensei has a happy face, and Mel-senpai has a scared face, like 'Oh no.' Like 'No way.'
泣いちゃう！そうそうそうそうそう！これね、とある映画の有名な映画のミームでございます。
I'm gonna cry! Yes, exactly! This is a meme from a famous movie.
パーフェクト！パーフェクト！パチパチ！ありがとうございます！
Perfect! Perfect! Clap clap! Thank you very much!
さっきのもレリドーで回します！ありがとうございます！
We'll spin the Lallitour for the last one too! Thank you very much!
よろしくレリドー！やったー楽しい！キアラちゃんありがとう！ありがとうございます！メリークリスマス！
Please do Lallitour! Yay, so fun! Thank you, Kiara-chan! Thank you very much! Merry Christmas!
はあ、キアラちゃん楽しかったね！ありがとう！
Ah, Kiara-chan, that was so fun! Thank you!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ということで、二人目はね、また衣装を着替えようと思うので、お着替えしていきたいと思います！
So, for the second person, we're going to change outfits again,
so we'd like to go change!
お着替えタイムです！またねー！またねー！
It's outfit change time! See you later! See you later!
「ただいまー！」「おかえりー！」
"I'm home!" "Welcome back!"
着替えてきたよ。
We changed our clothes.
どうかな？
How is it?
雪だるまメルと、雪だるまチョコです。です！
It's Snowman Mel and Snowman Choco. Yes!
ということで、二人目早速呼んでいきましょう！
With that, let's call in our second guest right away!
それじゃあ、二人目…
Well then, the second person...
もしもーし！はーい！
Hello! Hii!
もぐもぐおかゆ〜 おかゆ〜 おかゆちゃん！ おかゆさま〜！
Mogumogu Okayu~ Okayu~ Okayu-chan! Okayu-sama~!
メルちゃん、ヤッホー！遊びに来たよ！
Mel-chan, yahhoo! I came to hang out!
待ってた！待ってたよ！
We've been waiting! We've been waiting for you!
ねぇ、めちゃくちゃさ、その雪だるま衣装めっちゃかわいい！ え、本当 に！？
Hey, that snowman outfit is super cute! Eh, really!?
うれしー！ねぇ、なんか雪だるまが… 1、2、3、4つぐらいついてる？
I'm so happy! Hey, like, are there 1, 2, 3,
4 snowmen attached?
ついてるついてる。
They are, they are.
ぶつかるかもしれないけどね。
Though we might bump into each other.
6個あるよ、6個。6個、1、2、3、4、5、6個だ！やった！やった！
There are 6, 6. Six, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6!
Yay! Yay!
ねぇ、二人でにさ、なんか私が指定したポーズをしてもらえるって聞いたんだけど、いいの？
Hey, I heard you two would do a pose I specified,
is that okay?
そうなの！ なに！？ 何々！？
That's right! What!? What what!?
なんか、チョコ先生とメルちゃんだとNGがなさそうよね。
Like, with Choco-sensei and Mel-chan,
it seems like there are no NGs.
なになに、何でもやっちゃうよ。
What what, we'll do anything.
えー、やってほしい！
Eh, I want you to do it!
どうしようかな。やっぱちょっとくっついて、かわいい「てぇてぇポーズ」をやってもらいたいから…
What should I do. I want you to get close
and do a cute "teetee pose", so...
じゃあ、めちゃぎゅって近づいて… くっついて？
Then, get super close... and cuddle?
二人で、うわあ！これはやばいです！これはやばいです！
The two of us, woah! This is dangerous!
This is dangerous!
ちょっと近づいてどうするの？おかゆさま！
What are you doing getting a bit closer?
Okayu-sama!
やばい、やばい、やばい！なにに？
Dangerous, dangerous, dangerous! What is?
やばいよ、これ！ なにに？正面向いてください！
This is dangerous! What is?
Please face the front!
正面向いてください！ なにがやばい？正面向いて！
Please face the front! What's dangerous?
Face the front!
なにかやばい。ねぇ！
Something's dangerous. Hey!
じゃあ、正面向いてにゃんにゃんポーズしてください。
Well then, face the front
and do a nyannyan pose.
はーい！ にゃん、にゃんにゃん、にゃんにゃん！
Okay! Nyan, nyannyan, nyannyan!
待って、さっきの刺激が強すぎて声枯れちゃったよ！おかゆちゃーん！
Wait, the previous stimulation was too strong,
my voice got hoarse! Okayu-chaan!
おかゆねこの仲間だにゃ？
Are you a comrade of Okayu cat?
かわいい！これからもチョコたちのこと養ってくれるにゃ？
Cute! Will you keep supporting
Choco and company?
ないにゃい！お肉2匹、2匹養ってあげるにゃよ！やったにゃよ！うれしい！
Meow! I'll feed two pieces of meat,
two of them! Yay! I'm happy!
一緒に寝てくれるにゃ？ おお、いいにゃよ！
Will you sleep with me? Oh, sure!
なんでも、全肯定おかゆちゃん。
Anything goes, all-approving Okayu-chan.
いや、でもメルちゃんとチョコ先生を養うの中苦しそうだな。
Well, but supporting Mel-chan and Choco-sensei
sounds tough.
いや、何言ってるの！ メル、そんなに手間かかんないよ。
Hey, what are you saying!
Mel doesn't take that much trouble.
確かにチョコ先生が一番重そうだな。
True, Choco-sensei looks the heaviest.
確かに確かに！ チョコはちゃんと温めて寝かせるわよ。
True, true! Choco will properly warm you up
and put you to sleep.
本当に？ 暖かいの？ チョコ回路。
Really? Is it warm? Choco warmer.
チョコ回路。にゃんにゃん。チョコ回路。
Choco warmer. Meow meow. Choco warmer.
え、どうしようかな。じゃあ次は、え、後ろ向いて… 後ろ向いて…
Uh, what should I do. Then next,
um, turn around... turn around...
お尻ふりふりとかどうですか？
How about shaking your butt?
お尻ふりふり！ お尻ふりふり、お尻ふりふり！ おかゆふりふり、おかゆふりふり…
Shaking butts! Butt shaking, butt shaking!
Okayu shaking, Okayu shaking...
あーちょっと、カメラマンさん、際どいですよ、際どいですよ！ちょっと下げすぎ、下げすぎ！
Ah wait, cameraman-san, that's risky,
that's risky! Lowering it too much, too much!
かわいい！
Cute!
え、じゃあ最後は、え、こっち向いて、カメラに向かって、投げキッスでお願いします！ はい！
Um, then for the last one, um, face this way,
look at the camera, and do a blow kiss please! Okay!
おかゆ大好きよ。 おかゆちゃーん！
I love you, Okayu. Okayu-chaan!
うわぁ、大好き！
Woah, I love it!
うわぁ！
Woah!
かわいすぎです！
So cute!
やった！やった！ありがとう、おかゆちゃん！ ありがとう！ありがとう！
Yay! Yay! Thank you, Okayu-chan!
Thank you! Thank you!
なんか一生ですわよ、これは。
This is for a lifetime, huh.
バイバーイ！またねー！ありがとう！
Bye-bye! See you later! Thank you!
にゃんにゃん！にゃんにゃん！
Meow meow! Meow meow!
おかゆさん、いつも通り癒やされるね。
Okayu-san, so healing as usual.
じゃあ最後の生着替え行きましょうか！
Shall we go to our final live outfit change?
はい！行ってきまーす！
Yes! We're going!
呼んでみますか？
Shall we call her?
誰なのかなあ？
Who could it be?
誰か…もしもし？もしもしー！
Someone... Hello? Hello-!
こんこんみー！こんこんみー！
Konkonmi! Konkonmi!
待ってた、待ってた！待ってたよ！
We've been waiting for you!
いやもうそのリボンちょっと可愛すぎやしませんか？
Isn't that ribbon just way too cute?
お揃いなの。お揃いなの。
We match. We match.
めっちゃめちゃ可愛い、もうこれ、ありがとうございます！
It's super-duper cute, thank you so much!
嬉しい！嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
えっ、なんか今日はもうラミィの好きなポーズを２人がとってくれるって聞いたんですけど。
Wait, I heard the two of you would do Lamy's favorite poses today.
お任せしてよ、プロデューサー！
Leave it to us, Producer!
プロデューサー！
Producer!
プロデューサーちゃん可愛いか？
Producer-chan, are we cute?
めちゃけっこういいですか？早速いいですか？
Is it pretty good? Can we do it right away?
はい！
Yes!
えじゃあちょっと２人が迎え合わせみたいな感じで、膝立ちで、
Um, then, can you two face each other in a kneeling position
座ってもらっていいですか？
and sit down?
あ、そうそうそう！あ、そうそう！あー、いいよ！
Ah, yes, yes! Ah, yeah! Ah, good!
で、こっちちょっとこう２人が抱き合う感じで、
And then, like, hugging each other a bit,
あー、そうそうそう！あ、そうそう！あー、いいね！
Ah, yes, yes, yes! Ah, yeah! Ah, nice!
チョコ先生ちょっとこっちを向いて、
Choco-sensei, turn this way a bit,
あー、うわ目線、たまらん！
ah, wow, that upward gaze is irresistible!
あー、カメラマンさん、いいよ、いいよ！
Ah, cameraman-san, good, good!
そこですごくこうドキドキ、クリスマスみたいな、なんかちょっと一言もらってもいいですか？
Can you give us a word while feeling super excited, like Christmas?
ちかい。メリークリスマス、チョコ先生。メリークリスマス、メルちゃんな。
Close. Merry Christmas, Choco-sensei. Merry Christmas, Mel-chan.
大好き！あー、ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
I love you! Ah, thank you so much!
そしたらね、ちょっと、そう、可愛い感じ、あー、たまらん！
And then, like, a cute vibe—ah, I can't take it!
え、ちょっと、引っ張ってもらって。
Um, pull back a bit.
はい。やっぱね、２人にちょっとこう下からも見たいので、
Right. After all, we want to see the two of you from below too,
え、近づいてもらって。
so... come closer.
２人にこう近づいてもらって、カメラマンさん下からアオル感じで！
Come closer to each other, cameraman-san, from a low angle!
あー、いいね、いいね！あーちょっと、そのアオリが、アオリ顔で！
Ah, nice, nice! Ah, wait, that low-angle look, with that upward gaze!
あー、いいね、いいですね、そこまで！
Ah, nice, good, right there!
どうなる？どうなる？もっとかかってこいよ！
What's happening? Come at me more!
もっとこのちょっとギリギリを攻める感じにこうちょっと煽ってもらっていいですか？下から、カメラマンさん。
Can you egg us on even more to push the absolute limit? From below, cameraman-san.
もっと下ですね。はい、もっと上、もっと上。もっともっと、もっと！
Lower. Yes, higher, higher. More, more, more!
あー、もう大きいものでもメル先輩の顔が見えない！ちょっと下から見たら不気味になっちゃうでしょ？
Ah, with something big, Mel-senpai's face isn't even visible! If you look from below, it's creepy, right?
あー、ごめんなさい、すいません！
Ah, I'm sorry, my bad!
ちょっと引いて、もうちょい下、もうちょい下。もっと引いて、もっと引いて。
Pull back a bit, a bit lower. Pull back more, pull back more.
メルの方が身長小さいから見えちゃうの！
Mel is shorter, so you can see her!
もっとちょっと、引いてもらったほうがいいですね。
It's better if you pull back a bit more.
あ、そうですね。そうそうそうそうそうそうそう！メルさん、あ、メル先輩、危ない危ない危ない！メルさん、今度お尻！お尻出してますけど、そんなだめだよ！だめだめだめだめ！
Ah, is that so. Yes, yes, yes! Mel-san, ah, Mel-senpai, dangerous! Mel-san, now your butt! You're showing your butt, you can't do that!
もう、ありがとうございます！
Alright, thank you so much!
そしたら、もうじゃあ、え、とびきりの笑顔で、え、メリークリスマスと言ってもらってもいいですか？
Then, finally, can you say Merry Christmas with your absolute best smile?
はーい！ラミィちゃん、メリークリスマス！メリークリスマス！メリークリスマス！大成功、ありがとうございます！
Okay! Lamy-chan, Merry Christmas! Merry Christmas! Merry Christmas! Huge success, thank you so much!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
さあ、次の曲に行こうか！行こうか！
Now, let's go to the next song! Shall we go?
聞いて 会えない日の分だって
Listen, even for the days we can't meet,
少し困るくらいに 抱きしめて
hold me tight enough to trouble me a little.
ねえ、ちゃんと言ってよね 受け取って
Hey, say it properly and accept it,
甘く とろけちゃうような 時を
a time so sweet it melts away.
疲れてる顔して いつもたくさん頑張ってるね
You look tired, always working so hard.
もう全部任せて 全部食べてあげようか
Leave everything to me, shall I eat it all up for you?
よそ見なんて駄目だよ ちゃんとこっち向いていなくちゃ
No looking away, you have to look right at me.
目と目が合うでしょ 手ぇつないで 見つめてね
Our eyes will meet, holding hands, gazing at me.
よそ見なんて駄目だよ ちゃんとこっち向いていなくちゃ
No looking away, you have to look right at me.
目と目が合うでしょ 手ぇつないで 見つめてね
Our eyes will meet, holding hands, gazing at me.
ひとつ 胸を熱くさせて
One, letting my heart grow warm,
ふたつ 見つけてね
two, find it.
気まぐれにMy Way 繰り出して
On a whim, my own way, stepping out
追い越し追い越されそうな25時
Racing past and nearly passed at 1 AM
不真面目にNonsense ぶつけ合って繋がっていたい
Nonchalantly throwing nonsense, wanting to connect
FantaStreamer
ぐるぐるぐる と
Round and round...
目まぐるしい声に流され
Swept away by dizzying voices
数に毒されちゃってんの？
Getting poisoned by numbers?
待ちに待っていたこの瞬間
This moment I've waited and waited for
たまんなくしたいから
Is irresistible, so
身体全て捧げよう
I'll give my whole body to it
thumb up! c’mon babe
Thumb up! C'mon babe
follow! raise me up now
寝ぼけたeyes夢中にしたい
Sleepy eyes, I want to captivate them
途切れやしないように
So it never breaks off
trap & hells around, but
譲れない今だけは
Only this moment I won't yield
鳴りやまない
It won't stop ringing
でも足りないレスは生きるenergy
But lacking responses is life's energy
足下にRun Way続く方へ
Toward where the runway continues at my feet
駆け上がる情熱はStreamer
The passion surging up is Streamer
my name is FantaStreamer
誰もみんなaddictにしちゃいたいんだ
I want to make everyone an addict
即興vamp up vamp up vamp up vamp Vampire
Impromptu vamp up vamp up vamp up vamp Vampire
c’mon let it go
C'mon let it go
only but lonely なDreamer
Only but lonely dreamer
彼もみんな融かしていくようなテンション
A tension that melts everyone away
vamp up vamp up vamp up all right?
Ready, steady, getting, setting, go!
Don’t miss next show ほら
Don't miss next show, hey
Don’t miss next show
Don't miss next show
Don’t miss next show ほら
Don't miss next show, hey
Don’t miss next show
Don't miss next show
FantaStreamer
toxic な relation で
In a toxic relation
朝も夕もなくなっちゃってさ
Morning and evening are gone
どう する? やっぱ こう する?
What to do? Or maybe this?
無理しないように let go
Let go so you don't overdo it
そんじゅ 最初 は? そう my turn
Then first is? Right, my turn
お次 は? そう your turn
Next is? Right, your turn
共に up & down で go
Go together up & down
今っきゃ ないんだ showtime
It's showtime right now
宙に 舞う ような 蜜 の 味
The taste of honey dancing in the air
オーディ エンス の 歓び
The audience's joy
一度 食べ たら もう 最後
Once you eat it, that's it
嘲笑う 声 かき消し て
Drowning out mocking voices
もう 限界 ギリ まで 身体 預け 語ろう
Entrust your body to the limit and speak
戸惑い は no way
Hesitation is no way
認め 合っ て 競い合う 本能 は streamer
Instinct to acknowledge and compete is streamer
脆弱 な fanta streamer
Fragile fanta streamer
キミ の 声 に addict し ちまっ た ん だ
Got addicted to your voice
存外 vamp up vamp up vamp up vamp vampire
Surprisingly vamp up vamp up vamp up vamp vampire
c’mon let it go
C'mon let it go
lovely but tricky な believer
Lovely but tricky believer
これもみんなアタシの一部さ all right?
This is all part of me too, all right?
vamp up vamp up vamp up
語り明かせ
Talk through the night
wake up! turn it up
give a boost, your hands up!
消し去りたい でも愛したい
Want to erase it, but want to love it
過去やプライドも
Past and pride too
kick & boos around, but
今この瞬間を進め
Move forward in this very moment
見つめる eyes大事にしたい
Gazing eyes, I want to cherish them
今を生きる streamer
Streamer living in the present
don’t stop the sound
Don't stop the sound
もう迷わない streamer
No longer hesitating streamer
don’t stop the shout
Don't stop the shout
想い残さないように
So there are no regrets left
don’t stop the sound
Don't stop the sound
突き進むんだよ streamer
Keep pushing forward, streamer
don’t stop the shout
Don't stop the shout
3, 2, 1
my name is FantaStreamer
誰もみんなaddictにしちゃいたいんだ
I want to make everyone an addict
即興vamp up vamp up vamp up vamp Vampire
Impromptu vamp up vamp up vamp up vamp Vampire
c’mon let it go
C'mon let it go
only but lonely なDreamer
Only but lonely dreamer
彼もみんな融かしていくようなテンション
A tension that melts everyone away
vamp up vamp up vamp up 正体 は
Vamp up vamp up vamp up, the true identity is
幸福な fanta streamer
A blissful fanta streamer
キミ の 声 が 繋ぎ止め る ん だ
Your voice is what keeps it connected
存在 vamp up vamp up vamp up vamp vampire
Existence vamp up vamp up vamp up vamp vampire
c’mon let it go
C'mon let it go
only but lonely なDreamer
Only but lonely dreamer
まだまだ足りないみたいだ
Seems like it's still not enough
おいでで vamp up vamp up vamp up all right?
Come on, vamp up vamp up vamp up all right?
Ready, steady, getting, setting, go!
Don’t miss next show ほら
Don't miss next show, hey
Don’t miss next show
Don't miss next show
私のこと 知ってますか
Do you know about me?
可愛く見えてますか
Do I look cute to you?
私の歌 どうだろうな
I wonder how my song sounds
上手に歌えてますか
Am I singing it well?
衣装だとか メイクだとか
Costumes or makeup,
可愛く見えてますか
Do they look cute to you?
振り付けとか ファンサとかも
Choreography or fan service too,
喜んでもらえますか
Can I make you happy with them?
照れ冷めたくなって 足は震える
Growing shy and cold, my legs tremble
それでも戦いたい アイドルだから
Even so, I want to fight, because I'm an idol
バカにする奴は嫌いだ
I hate people who make fun of me
肉付けされるのも嫌いだ アイドルなんかという言葉は
I hate being stereotyped too, words like "just an idol"
見てもいないくせに言うな 頑張りを求めないような
Don't talk without watching, don't demand hard work
姫ageとか強要するな アイドルなんかという言葉はこの世で一番大嫌いだ
Don't force princess treatment, I hate words like "just an idol" the most in this world
つらいデートで見えないから分からないと思います
It's hard to see on a date so you might not understand
アイドルなんて呼ばないで
Don't call me an idol,
Don't call me an idol.
私はいつでも あなたを見てる
I am always watching you.
学校に行く途中で 待ち伏せる
Lying in wait on my way to school,
どんな男にも 興味がない
No matter what kind of guy comes along,
I'm not interested.
携帯で隠し撮りされたって
Even if you secretly take pictures of me with your phone,
きっとそっけない表情でしょう
My expression is probably cold and indifferent.
愛されるより 愛したいの
Rather than being loved, I want to love,
遠い場所から 憧れてる
Admiring from afar.
人には言えない 片思い
A one-sided love I can't tell anyone about.
アイドルだって恋をする
An idol falls in love, too,
年頃になれば みんなと同じ
When we reach that age.
嬉しい時は微笑んで 悲しい時は涙する
Smiling when we're happy, and crying when we're sad,
私も普通の女の子です
I'm just an ordinary girl, too.
手紙やプレゼントを渡されても
Being handed letters and gifts,
握手することに慣れてない
I'm not used to shaking hands.
彼らが夢見てる女の子
The girl they dream of,
そんなお人形になれないから
I can't be a doll like that.
もっと自由に恋をしたい
I want to fall in love more freely,
ピュアなイメージは 息苦しい
A pure image is suffocating.
そのうちエッチもしてみたい
Before long, I want to try kissing, too.
アイドルなんて呼ばないで
Don't call me an idol,
Don't call me an idol.
ホントは架空の恋人だけど
Actually, I'm just a fictional lover,
心の中に現れる
Appearing deep inside my heart,
やさしい星の王子様
A gentle prince of the stars.
私はいつでもあなたを見てる
I am always watching you.
la la la la la
私は絶対におほし…じゃなくて、アイドルじゃない
I am definitely not an idol.
アイドルなんて呼ばないで
Don't call me an idol,
Don't call me an idol.
ホントは架空の恋人だけど
Actually, I'm just a fictional lover,
心の中に現れる
Appearing deep inside my heart,
やさしい星の王子様
A gentle prince of the stars.
私はいつでもあなたを見てる
I am always watching you.
la la la la la
あなた
You...
あなただけのアイドルになる
Your and only your idol!
スタッフさんの愛があって
With staff's love,
いつも家族の愛があって
With family's love,
生きてる
Living on,
アイドル
Idol!
バカにするやつは嫌いだ
Anyone who makes fun of me is hated,
見下されるのも嫌いだ
Anyone who looks down on me is hated.
アイドルなんかという言葉は
Words like "idol",
この世で一番大嫌いだ
I don't even want to hear them!
口では嫌いだ決めるんだ
Even though I say that,
アイドルになんかなるもんか
Playing hard to get,
アイドルなんかという言葉は
Words like "idol",
この世で一番大嫌いだ
I don't even want to hear them!
アイドルなんて呼ばないで
Don't call me an idol,
Don't call me an idol.
(間奏)
(Instrumental outro)
放課後 二人で過ごした教室
In the classroom where we spent time after school,
机の上 夢中ではずむ君の声
Your lively voice is on my desk.
無頓着な君のその態度が
That oblivious attitude of yours
いつも私を意地悪にさせるの
Always puts me in a playful mood.
ひとりぼっちと思う時もある
There are times when I feel all alone,
涙止められない日もある
And times when I can't stop the tears.
本当の私を見つめてほしいの
I want you to see the real me,
きっと伝わると信じているよ
And I believe those feelings will reach you.
君はいつでもいつまでも変わらないから
Because you never ever change,
私が何度も何度もシグナル送ってあげる
I'll send a signal to you time and time again.
夢見たあの丘目指して
Aiming for that hill where we dreamed,
くじけそうな時も 頑張れそうだよ
I can keep going even when I feel like giving up,
君がいるから
Because you're here with me.
本当の私を見つめてほしいの
I want to gaze at the real you,
きっと伝わると信じているよ
Believing that one day it will reach you.
君はいつだっていつだって変わらないから
You never, ever change,
私が何回も何回もシグナルを送ってあげる
So I'll keep sending signals to you.
夢見たあの丘目指して
I remember that day,
シグナル送ってあげる
Sending signals over and over...
夢見た あの日目指して
When I was about to break down,
君がいるから
I did my best because you were there.
ふたり 歩くいつもの帰り道
On the road where we always walk home together,
名前のない気持ちが芽生え始めている
Nameless feelings are starting to sprout.
だけど踏み出すための勇気は
But the courage to take a step forward
少しだけまだ遠くにある
Is still a little too far away.
何も持っていなかった私に
When I had nothing at all,
君がくれた心の鍵は
The key to my heart you gave me
胸の奥で眠っていた
Was sleeping deep inside my chest.
二人 歩くいつもの帰り道
Walking together on our usual way home,
名前のない気持ちが芽生え始めている
Nameless feelings are starting to sprout.
だけど踏み出すための勇気は
The courage to take that step forward
少しだけまだ遠くにある
Is still a little too far away.
何も持っていなかった私に
The key to my heart you gave me
君がくれた心の鍵は
Brings the warmth of spring.
胸の奥で眠っていた
Thinking of you always,
何も持っていなかった私に
I hope one day you'll truly understand.
君がくれた心の鍵は胸の奥で眠っていた
The future we dreamed of together...
放課後 二人で過ごした教室
After school, the classroom where we spent time together
机の上 夢中ではずむ君の声
Your voice bouncing enthusiastically on the desk
鈍感な君のその態度が
Your overly insensitive attitude
いつも私を意地悪にさせるの
Always makes me want to tease you
君をいつだっていつだって思ってるから
Because I am always, always thinking of you
きっとねいつの日かちゃんと分かってほしい
Surely, someday, I want you to understand properly
二人で描いた未来をもっと近い距離で見つめられるように
So I can gaze at the future we drew from a closer distance
夢見てるから
Because I'm dreaming
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
メルさは！これからもよろしくね！
Mel-sama! Keep up the good work!
チョコセンセー！こちらこそ！
Choco-sensei! Likewise!
あの日触れた君のシグナル
The signal of yours I touched that day
始まりの扉が開くよ
The door of the beginning will open
(あのね)
You know
君はいつだっていつだって変わらないでね
You are always, always unchanged, right?
私に何度も何度もシグナル送って
Send me signals over and over again
ほしい
I want you to send them to me
輝くあの虹のように
Like that shining rainbow
涙のあとも奇跡に変えるよ
Even the traces of tears turn into a miracle
君はいつだっていつだって変わらないから
Because you are always, always unchanged
私が何度も何度もシグナル送ってあげる
I will send you signals over and over again
夢見たあの丘目指して
Aimed at the hill I dreamed of
くじけそうなときも頑張れそうだよ
Even when I feel discouraged, I can do my best
君がいるから
Because you are here
ここまでいっぱい曲聴いてもらったけど、みんなどうだった？
You listened to a lot of songs so far, how was everyone?
どうだったかな？
How was it?
めっちゃ盛り上げてくれるじゃん！
You guys are hyping us up so much!
え、そんなによかった？
Eh, was it really that good?
めっちゃ嬉しい！メルもめっちゃ嬉しい！
I'm so happy! Mel is so happy too!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
でね、でもそろそろ終盤になってきたんだけど
And you know, we're getting close to the end now
えー！はやーい！
Eh! So fast!
ここで、なんと重大発表です！
And now, a major announcement!
なんと！メルキス3周年記念グッズが発売されます！
The Melkiss 3rd anniversary merchandise will be released!
やったーー！！うれしーー！！
Yay!! So happy!!
まず、一つ目は！
First of all, the first item is...
コップ！私たちとおそろいのメルキスコップが……こちら！
A cup! The matching Melkiss cup is... right here!
かわいいーー！かわいい！
So cute!! Cute!
一緒に使って乾杯しよう！
Let's use it together and toast!
乾杯ー！乾杯ー！
Cheers! Cheers!
そして、二つ目は……こちら！メルキスの可愛いロゴが入ったTシャツを！
And the second is... right here! A T-shirt with the cute logo!
これ寝巻きとかにお出かけも一緒！
You can wear this to sleep or go out together!
黒と白があるよ。
There's black and white.
いやあ、もう2色ね、揃えちゃおうね！
Man, let's get both colors!
お揃いにしちゃおう！お揃いにしちゃおう！
Let's match! Let's match!
双子コーデで手をつなぐのもできるよ！
You can hold hands in matching twin outfits too!
最高じゃーん！
That's the best!!
そして、三つ目は！たや先生描き下ろし！メルキスアクリルジオラマスタンド！
And third! Taya-sensei's Melkiss acrylic diorama stand!
やったーー！！めっちゃくちゃ可愛い！
Yay!! Super duper cute!
この3体……じゃなくて3アイテムはオリジナルで考えていただいたんですよ！
These 3 items were custom-designed for us!
めっちゃ可愛いじゃん！可愛いー！
So cute!
メルたちをおうちににお迎えしてね！
Welcome us into your home!
さらに！さらに！
Furthermore! Furthermore!
今回は数量限定で直筆サイン入り全部セットが販売されるよ！
This time, a complete set with handwritten signatures will be sold!
おー
Oh!
最後まで楽しもう！
Let's have fun until the end!
いくわよ！
Here we go!
chu - chu - chu - chu とろけそう で
chu-chu-chu-chu, melting away,
chu - chu - chu - chu 甘く fancy
chu-chu-chu-chu, sweetly fancy,
chu - chu - chu - chu 口づけ を
chu-chu-chu-chu, with a kiss,
チョコ メルティ
Choco Melty!
ほんの 少し お 疲れ の 日々 は
On days when you're just a little tired,
幸せ の 箱 開け ちゃおう
Let's open up a box of happiness!
甘い その 誘惑 も 乗っかってみる の
Why not give in to that sweet temptation?
お疲れ様です 乾杯 ！
Good work, let's toast!
か ぷっと 噛み付く よ キミ の ハート
I'll take a bite right into your heart,
もっともっと 好き に なって ね
So grow to love me more and more!
不器用 だけど 愛して ね
I'm clumsy, but please love me.
fight , oh , fight , oh
Fight, oh! Fight, oh!
さあ みんなで ！
Now, everyone together!
（ チョコ 先生 また お菓子 散乱 し てる ！）
(Hey Choco-sensei, you scattered snacks again!)
（ あら 気付か なかっ たわぁ つい 楽しく なっ ちゃって ）
(Oh, I didn't notice! I just got too carried away.)
（ メル 様 これ は ？）
(Mel-sama, what's this?)
（ これ は 生き血 だよ … ！）
(This is my lifeblood...!)
（ もう かぷっちゃう ぞ ！ あ 、 始まっちゃう ！）
(I'm gonna gobble you up! Ah, it's starting!)
（ じゃあ 行き ます かぁ ！）
(Shall we go then?!)
私たち と 踊り ましょう
Let's dance together with us,
今日 も 明後日 も
Today and the day after tomorrow,
メリー メルティ な 恋 とな
In a merry-melty romance.
チョコ と キャラメル 召し上がれ
Enjoy some chocolate and caramel!
甘美 な この 物語 を
Follow this sweet story
ずっと ついてきて （ どこまでも ）
And keep following me (wherever we go).
サニー ラッキー な 日々 を
Through sunny, lucky days,
キミ と 見つめあう 未来 で （ 私たち と ）
In a future gazing at you (together with us).
さあ よろしく どうぞ
Now, nice to meet you.
chu - chu - chu - chu とろけそう で
chu-chu-chu-chu, melting away,
chu - chu - chu - chu 甘く fancy
chu-chu-chu-chu, sweetly fancy,
chu - chu - chu - chu ちょっと 苦い
chu-chu-chu-chu, slightly bitter,
チョコ メルティ
Choco Melty!
ああ 一息 ついて いかない ？ 頑張りすぎ も 毒 だし
Ah, won't you take a break? Working too hard is toxic too,
苦く も 甘い 誘惑 も 受け入れて ね
So accept both bitter and sweet temptations.
ご苦労様です alright !
Good work, alright!
診て あげるわ キミ の ハート
I'll examine your heart,
ほんの ちょっと 照れくさい かな
Though it's a tiny bit embarrassing,
私 だけ を 愛して
Love only me.
fight , oh , fight , oh
Fight, oh! Fight, oh!
さあ みんなで ！
Now, everyone together!
（ ねえ メル 様 、 お腹 空いた 、 何か 持って ない ？ ）
(Hey Mel-sama, I'm hungry, do you have anything?)
（ なんで こんな 時 に ！ どうでも いい よ ！ これ でも 食べて て ）
(Why at a time like this?! Whatever! Just eat this.)
（ ちょ 、 これ ツブコーン じゃん ！ しかも 食べ物 じゃ ない し ）
(Hey, this is corn kernels! And it's not even food!)
（ 細かい … ）
(So picky...)
（ 私 コーン は ちょっと … ）
(I'm not big on corn...)
（ あの ねえ … ）
(Umm...)
（ あ 、 後半戦 行き ましょう ！）
(Ah, let's head to the second half!)
私たち と しゃしゃり ましょう
Let's be flashy together with us,
いつ も いつまで も
Always and forever,
メリー メルティ な 恋 かな
In a merry-melty romance.
ショコラ と ココア で 召し上がれ
Enjoy some chocolate and cocoa!
悪戯 な この レシピ を
Follow this mischievous recipe
もっと ついてきて （ どこまでも ）
And keep following me (wherever we go).
happy lucky な 日々 を
Through happy, lucky days,
終わり の ない この 未来 で （ 私たち と ）
In an endless future (together with us).
さあ ずっと 続く よ
Now, it will go on forever.
（ ここ に 居る こと が ただただ うれしく て ）
(Just being here makes me so happy,)
（ この 大切 な 時間 が 止まって ほしく て ）
(I want this precious time to stop.)
（ あなた に 出会え た こと ）
(Meeting you,)
（ あなた に 見つけて もらえ た こと ）
(Being found by you,)
（ 甘く て 淡い 最高 の 出会い を ）
(Let's make this sweet and tender best encounter—)
１ 両手 広げて
1. Spread your arms wide,
２ 胸 に 抱きしめて
2. Hold them close to your chest,
３ 最後に 笑顔 で
3. And finally, with a smile,
ワクワク キラキラ ドキドキ すべて 手 に して
Thrilling, sparkling, and heart-pounding, grab it all!
もしもし この 夢 が 叶う と する ならば
If this dream were to come true,
幸せ の 型 作って ビター でも シュガー でも
Let's mold happiness, whether bitter or sweet,
今日 も 明後日 も merry melty な 恋 ？
Today and the day after tomorrow, a merry melty romance?
チョコ と キャラメル 召し上がれ
Enjoy some chocolate and caramel!
甘美 な この 物語 を
Follow this sweet story
ずっと ついてきて （ どこまでも ）
And keep following me (wherever we go).
sunny lucky な 日々 を
Through sunny, lucky days,
君 と 見つめあう 未来 で （ 私たち と ）
In a future gazing at you (together with us).
さあ よろしく どうぞ
Now, nice to meet you.
chu - chu - chu - chu とろけそう で
chu-chu-chu-chu, melting away,
chu - chu - chu - chu 甘く fancy
chu-chu-chu-chu, sweetly fancy,
chu - chu - chu - chu ちょっと 苦い 合言葉
chu-chu-chu-chu, a slightly bitter password,
chu - chu - chu - chu メロメロ で
chu-chu-chu-chu, completely dazed,
chu - chu - chu - chu 刺激 的 な
chu-chu-chu-chu, exhilarating,
chu - chu - chu - chu 口づけ を
chu-chu-chu-chu, with a kiss,
choco melty
ほんの 少し お 疲れ の 日々 は
On days when you're just a little tired,
幸せ の 箱 開け ちゃおう
Let's open up a box of happiness!
甘い その 誘惑 も 乗っかってみる の
Why not give in to that sweet temptation?
ご苦労様です alright !
Good work, alright!
診て あげるわ キミ の ハート
I'll examine your heart,
ほんの ちょっと 照れくさい かな
Though it's a tiny bit embarrassing,
私 だけ を 愛して
Love only me.
fight , oh , fight , oh
Fight, oh! Fight, oh!
さあ みんなで ！
Now, everyone together!
１ 両手 広げて
1. Spread your arms wide,
２ 胸 に 抱きしめて
2. Hold them close to your chest,
３ 最後に 笑顔 で
3. And finally, with a smile,
ワクワク キラキラ ドキドキ すべて 手 に して
Thrilling, sparkling, and heart-pounding, grab it all!
もしもし この 夢 が 叶う と する ならば
If this dream were to come true,
幸せ の 型 作って ビター でも シュガー でも
Let's mold happiness, whether bitter or sweet,
今日 も 明後日 も merry melty な 恋 ？
Today and the day after tomorrow, a merry melty romance?
チョコ と キャラメル 召し上がれ
Enjoy some chocolate and caramel!
甘美 な この 物語 を
Follow this sweet story
ずっと ついてきて （ どこまでも ）
And keep following me (wherever we go).
幸せ の 型 作って
Let's build happiness together,
ビター でも シュガー でも
No matter whose sugar or spice it may be,
今日 も 明後日 も
Today and the day after tomorrow,
chu - chu - chu - chu とろけそう で
chu-chu-chu-chu, melting away,
chu - chu - chu - chu 甘く fancy
chu-chu-chu-chu, sweetly fancy,
chu - chu - chu - chu 口づけ を
chu-chu-chu-chu, with a kiss,
チョコ メルティ
Choco Melty!
ほんの 少し お 疲れ の 日々 は
On days when you're just a little tired,
幸せ の 箱 開け ちゃおう
Let's open up a box of happiness!
ご苦労様です alright !
Good work, alright!
診て あげるわ キミ の ハート
I'll examine your heart,
ほんの ちょっと 照れくさい かな
Though it's a tiny bit embarrassing,
私 だけ を 愛して
Love only me.
fight , oh , fight , oh
Fight, oh! Fight, oh!
さあ みんなで ！
Now, everyone together!
chu - chu - chu - chu メロメロ で
chu-chu-chu-chu, melo-melo,
chu - chu - chu - chu 刺激 的 な
chu-chu-chu-chu, exhilarating,
chu - chu - chu - chu 口づけ を
chu-chu-chu-chu, with a kiss,
チョコ メルティ
Choco Melty!
よっしゃ 行く ぞ ！
Here we go!
choco melty
メルキュウ♡3周年LIVE Xmas Party
MelKey ♡ 3rd Anniversary LIVE Xmas Party